MY BELOVED DEMON
Do as you like.
Because it's better for me.
They are all dead.
Ms. Chu,
mom and dad
Everyone I loved in my life is dead.
And you will die too...
through me
I don't care.
your wound
It cannot be wetted.
You…
Your strength...
My powers...
returned
EPISODE 9
THE UNCOVERED TRUTH
That's why...
do people deliberately do stupid things?
What happened?
When did you wake up?
It's been a long time.
Did I snore?
- I wouldn't be against the worst.
- Did I snore?
- No.
- Exactly?
Yes. So let me see your face.
No.
Why not?
I don't know. I feel a little embarrassed.
Let's go somewhere. I'm hungry
I thought you had enough
cups of hand-brewed coffee.
I know Maybe it's because
that I am almost human now.
You didn't book the whole restaurant today.
i realized
which might not be such a bad idea
to eat among people.
When there are so many of them around
it's cute and lively.
One double order.
I'm afraid it's only available for Christmas, sir.
But that is the reason we are here.
Can it not be considered
what is christmas today
To mark
my stay among people.
No ingredients sir.
Exactly?
Then let's find another institution,
where paired dishes are served.
Just two of these, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Isn't this discrimination against demons?
Why paired dishes
only on Jesus' birthday?
Let's go back to Christmas
and let's celebrate with your favorite cake.
You tell the demon
celebrate the birth of Jesus?
So you don't want to?
No, I didn't say that.
Not that I don't want to. Just said so.
But why is everyone so excited about Christmas?
For some reason, Christmas brings joyous excitement.
It's like becoming a child again.
now i understand
why is everyone so noisy
and intemperate at Christmas.
i will try my best
as my name suggests.
I don't want to brag
but somehow I was wooed by a chaebol.
The famous heiress
fell in love with me at first sight
and chased
for us to register the marriage.
But I told her:
"I refuse to be a chaebol dog.
I will be the hunting dog of the public."
I refused her so coldly and decisively.
A hunting dog?
Is that why you're trying to sniff everything out?
Maybe we will continue elsewhere?
Yes, love at first sight.
- Give me the wrist.
- Why?
To teach him
not to talk about you.
He wants to be a hunting dog,
then I can give him a nose…
leave it
That's what I suggested
to register the marriage and refused.
Why do you side with that scoundrel?
How annoying.
By the way, did I tell you?
What did she tell me?
I don't go to work now.
The anniversary of the company's foundation.
Really?
What is going on anyway?
Why isn't Director Jeon happy,
that To To Hee resigned?
Shouldn't he be glad she's safe?
God
Is he still sleeping?
It's great not having to go to work.
I thought you liked going to work.
I thought so too
until she fell in love with a demon.
So what do people usually do on a date?
They usually eat and drink coffee.
And that's all.
How insignificant.
Even if with me?
What is it?
I'm at the door, Director Jon.
Open it.
I'm not at home now.
So where are you?
We are near the Khan River.
That's right. We are on a date.
- In your condition?
- I have completely recovered.
CALL COMPLETED
DIRECTOR CHON
What did I miss?
I am interested in this.
What kind of insignificant things are these?
- So?
- Yes.
These are bikes for couples.
Steam…
For couples?
Let's try to ride!
He is so insignificant.
I love insignificant things.
Come on.
- What?
- Numo.
Where are we going?
- Let's go get such a bike.
- But...
Why are you sitting in the front?
Wait, look!
- What?
- He is there!
Let's try that little thing.
Is everything for couples now?
Come on?
- Of course, let's go.
- Forward.
- That's right.
- Good.
- Forward.
- I raise my legs.
That's it.
- Higher!
- I say above!
- Up!
What could it be?
- Higher!
- What would be the most effective way
fool us while we relax?
- Higher!
- Maybe...
- It can't be.
- Even higher!
Then what about…
No, and not that.
My head is splitting, damn it.
I remember that I had a high IQ,
but did I drink too much?
It looks like all the brain cells have died.
Sneeze.
I would rather do than think.
- How cute.
- I like it here.
Artificial landscapes are the most beautiful.
Isn't it usually the other way around?
I prefer
created by people, not by God.
That's why I'm more of a collector,
than a traveler.
Don't you like God?
Does anyone like their boss?
Although I have never met God personally,
unable to bind.
And it didn't help that I'm 200 years old
watched the decline of the world.
I wonder what your life was like
the past 200 years.
An insignificant person
will never understand the experience of a demon.
I'm not trying to understand you.
I'm just trying
accept you as you are.
It seems that the demons were the guardians of mankind.
Really?
"Give me."
In ancient Greek it means
"to share the same fate."
The word "demon" comes from him.
"To share the same fate."
your truth
that we share the same fate.
Then how did demons become bad?
Let's say I succumbed to life's difficulties.
People turn to the dark side
after several years of work.
I had to do it for 200 years.
Looks like you're not that bad.
So you came back
to its original being.
You are my keeper.
Come on.
Okay.
Customer number 82, your paired drinks
and a gift soft toy are ready.
Thank you.
No, I'm thanking you.
It's starting to seem
that people are insignificant and at the same time charming.
It's like I took a kitten
and began to care
about all the homeless cats in the world.
Who knew attachment was contagious?
You're comparing me to a cat now
and not with a weasel beetle?
what do you want honey
Same as you dear.
Whatever you want to call a kitten,
maybe call "dear"?
No.
can you call me man
You must be crazy.
What are you talking about?
I am your husband.
- Let the kitten be better.
- No.
Look how beautiful it is.
Yes.
Seriously, she's forever noticing everything.
God
beautiful
And this one is beautiful.
All photos are flawless.
They are so photogenic.
God, what am I even doing?
I am not their photographer.
Pull yourself together, No Soo An.
You came to dig up the truth.
She can fool everyone, but not me.
To To Hee, time for you
show its true ugly face.
Why did you refuse to go?
on that little ferry?
Then. We have a lot of time.
When then?
Let's set a day.
Otherwise, you may have to wait another year...
Hey?
hello dear Mom is almost home.
Okay, see you later.
To To Hee.
What a scoundrel.
Ruined such a great song, didn't you?
Come on.
Don't like this music.
Why not? I like it.
I want to dance to something.
Shall we dance?
No, I'm clumsy.
Just listen to me.
When you dance in a couple,
you have to trust your partner.
Now this is our song.
What happened?
What the hell?
What is it?
I work hard here
and they enjoy themselves all day.
I give up.
It's uncharacteristic of me to work hard.
After all, I'm better at thinking than doing.
That's right. It's time for me to go.
Special meetings of shareholders
for the election of a new chairman, we will be able to
hold on earlier next week.
Spend this week.
It will be difficult.
A procedure must be followed when…
I pay you an abyss of money,
that you overcome such problems.
Let's accelerate events as much as possible.
As soon as you become the head,
I think your son will head Elektronika Mire.
There's something I've learned
while he was on a run
my mother is over 20 years old.
This is the importance of deprivation.
Deprivation leads to growth.
I plan to teach this son.
Nice shot!
17 YEARS AGO
I'm here, mom.
I have to wash it off.
Yes, I have to.
I have to wash
all your dirty sins.
If I don't wash it...
You know why mom
turned her back on us?
I think she didn't like us.
It was self-hatred.
She despised us
because she despised her own blood.
I think even such a fool as you
must realize that we
at an important crossroads.
We have to convince the public
that we have reliable
and a stable succession plan.
I understand.
I'm not like mom.
I will fix you and use you.
I would never trust that
who is not related to me by blood.
NOTICE
Do you have a second phone?
Just…
It is for girls.
Don't worry. I will fix everything.
EXECUTIVE
Why no word from you?
And do not say that you are leaving the game.
THE DEVIL
What a peaceful morning.
It hasn't been for a long time.
In the end, I did
I'm better, Ms. Chu.
I have always believed that happiness is not real.
You got up early.
I have to go to work.
I thought here.
Maybe let's say that yesterday was the eve,
and the anniversary of the company today?
No. Struggling to take a whole year off?
Anniversary deserves though
for two days of celebration.
It seems that you like company less than I do.
Favorite company?
Greetings, Ms. Sin.
Mrs. To, we received
a document from No Suk Min.
You can't sign it.
Everything is already over.
We have to catch the scoundrel
who tried to kill you
find who was behind it
and make sure that he will leave you.
I don't want to
Why not?
I have already fully recovered.
I don't want to start all over again.
I like the peace I have.
WAIVER OF INHERITANCE
RECEIVER:
TO TO HI
DIED:
CHU CHONG SUK
What is better for you
became what is best for me.
I decided to leave
that everyone finally finds peace,
and it turned out that I was the one who became happy.
You said that in the world
you have to pay for everything.
Happiness requires sacrifice.
And I think it's worth it.
To To Hee.
Are you really going to give up
without even knowing his face?
If you give up now
then you will live the rest of your life in fear.
You can't keep the peace by covering everything up.
Let's just see his face.
After that
I will do as you say.
OK.
I will see his face
and that's it, okay?
I've been by your side all day.
Why haven't I recharged?
Let's try again when you recharge.
Mr. Choo Seok Hoon has arrived.
Why does Choo Seok Hoon keep coming here?
It's somehow suspicious.
It's just illogical.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Jeon… No, Director Jeon.
He had just survived a deadly attack.
So how could he recover so quickly?
When you say it, something is definitely not right.
show me
Maybe the heavens helped him.
Or ancestors.
You and your superstitions.
Maybe he has a secret.
Secrecy?
Maybe he hides something medicinal.
What?
A mystery, right?
Deliciously.
Since I didn't come
for a meeting and all that,
I wanted to see you.
is everything ok
Yes.
I am much better than I expected.
What a relief.
Do you remember how you used to go with me?
to a tattoo parlor in the USA?
you said
that you are afraid of needles and will never get a tattoo.
I made him drunk.
I didn't even feel anything.
You often behave differently than usual
since I met Mr. Chong.
To Hee
You don't…
do you not regret your decision?
No, I don't regret it.
Thank you Seok Hoon.
And I'm sorry.
Mr. Chong
can we talk
He likes me too much.
How are you?
Like new.
You seemed to be in critical condition.
I usually recover quickly.
Vampires stay young
consuming people's blood.
What is your secret?
Delusional about vampires again?
Are you that interested in the occult?
I'm not interested in the occult.
I am interested in you, Mr. Chong.
You're in love with me, right?
Do you like men?
Mr. Chong
What do you get out of a relationship with To Hee?
I don't understand what's the use for you
that you are her husband and protector.
I need her.
If that were true,
you wouldn't sit and watch like her
gives up what is important to her
through you
Finally we are on the same page.
I don't plan to sit and watch.
Satisfied?
The secret of my recovery is a thirst for revenge.
There was no way I could die without paying back
to whoever did this to me.
TO TO HI
Now I am free.
I can finally go out without a bodyguard.
Greetings, madam.
Why don't we have a drink to celebrate?
I forgot how correct you are.
Let's do it.
But one drink at a time.
"MIRE GROUP" WILL ELECT A CHAIRMAN
AT THE SPECIAL MEETING OF SHAREHOLDERS
Looks like Ms. To has officially given up.
I don't think it should end like this.
Something is wrong here.
That's right.
When the speech has already come,
you can draw a photo robot
half of the face?
What do you say?
And you are talented.
More than it seems.
And what do I look like?
Well, look in the mirror.
The game of hide and seek is over.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
The boss works here.
Let's take care of safety and cleanliness here ourselves.
Synchronously!
Make sure the boss
did not inhale a single speck of dust!
- Move!
- Yes, sir!
who are you
- I am the assistant director here.
- Exactly?
Look, the proof is the bags under the eyes.
- Go through!
Director Chon.
You are needed in the theater.
Please drive these dogs out.
The boss has arrived.
Congratulations, boss.
- Congratulations, boss!
I said I'm not your boss.
What is illegal work?
A little You all worked so hard.
Please have a drink. Perfectly.
Drive these dogs out.
Performance coming soon. They scare the public.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
You call yourself "Tulkepa",
i.e. "Wild dogs"?
Yes, boss.
- Yes, boss!
Do you know what else your name sounds like?
"Tulkkepa" like sorghum and shallot seeds.
God
You're funny, boss.
Our name, Wild Dogs,
symbolizes our fearlessness and tenacity...
But we will become famous
as the soul of Korean cuisine,
Castor and shallot seeds!
- Castor and shallot seeds!
Come what may,
I have a task for you.
If you don't do it,
forbid you to appear before my eyes.
We are ready to risk our lives, boss!
- As you say, boss!
Ahead!
- Forward!
Director Jon, it seems
you solved the problem
Are you no longer her bodyguard and husband?
I warned you, didn't I?
after all i said
do you really want to become an insignificant person?
Do you know what it's like to be human?
Every day it seems that you are walking through a thin crisis,
and it seems to give us the right
hunt each other.
People are the most cowardly
and disgusting creatures in the world.
You were perfect because you were a demon.
Death, love, fear...
you were who you were
because he was free from all this.
stop it
There is no way I will back down from To To Hee.
And I will not back down from you.
I won't let you jump
to Gehenna of fire.
This is a final warning, Chin Ka-yeon.
Don't cross the line.
What is so special about it?
Why is it worth it
to risk everything for her?
Star Chin.
how about
to wish them both happiness?
If their happiness comes at too high a price,
this is not true happiness.
Allow me.
No, I will do it.
Cheers.
So nice to drink in the fresh air.
I'm glad you like it.
Finally my journey is complete
although its ending is unexpected.
It was easier to let go
than I thought
So I wonder
why did I hold on so tightly?
Sometimes we put everything on the line
not understanding why they made such a bet.
Maybe we'll find out
only at the end of the trip.
What could be the reason for my trip?
I don't know.
Mrs. Sin.
How was your marriage?
My ex was extremely rude.
I don't know if it is possible
to love and hate a person at the same time
in such a short period of time.
But now that it's over
I understand myself better.
If not for him
I would never understand what I am like in my soul
pathetic, primitive, weak and strong.
This is what my marriage meant to me.
I didn't know you were so passionate.
me too
I have never loved before or after him.
I have been warm all my life,
neither cold nor hot.
But I don't regret it, because it flared up once.
This is probably the reason for your trip.
That's right.
Growth is possible only after destruction.
Cheers.
Well, raise a glass.
To the bottom
She's so crazy
Where are you, man?
To To Hee, your husband…
The train of happiness starts To To Hee!
Ladies and gentlemen.
We are experiencing turbulence.
Turbulence.
Turbulence!
But they are really drunk like dogs.
What is To To Hee?
- Yes, Jon.
- What?
I'm sorry that I forced you forever
work late
Nothing.
You pay me just as much.
I think so.
- Here.
- To To Hee!
you better
get together
Hold on.
What is it?
Why do we laugh?
I don't mind.
- Let's be!
I am embarrassed for my wife.
Why don't we go home?
The sun rose.
It is so dazzling.
The sun rose
Shine, shine...
And Jon! Where are you going?
- Let's drink another glass.
- I need to go to work.
It's already 9:00. I was late.
I'm late!
What?
All people should be drunk with happiness!
Ahead!
OK!
We don't drink alcohol.
And happiness.
Time to drink!
Jung Ku Won!
you better
get together
Don't throw up your happiness!
Wait, sit down.
Mr. Puck, someone needs your help.
Hurry here.
is everything ok
To the bottom
Park Pshov Kyo.
you better
get together
My name is Pok Kyo, not Pshov Kyo.
Kyo left.
Come on.
Godi
male
ride me on your back
How much did you drink?
I feel extremely happy.
It's like a mountain off your shoulders.
I feel so free and happy.
And that makes me sick.
Because only I am happy.
I feel so sorry for Ms. Chu.
- Man, can I have another round?
- Yes?
Of course, but you know
how many laps have we done?
I don't mind.
Another round please?
Exactly?
Won't you do it for me man?
OK.
- Forward!
- Run!
- Okay, run?
- That's right.
- Run, demon, run!
You with your diligence.
You even seem diligent.
Listen.
And where is your apartment among all this?
Tell me where exactly you live.
Why do you want to know where I live?
To take you home.
What is it?
What kind of look is this?
You are a good man.
I'm just following Director Chong's order here.
And you are also responsible.
But you are joking.
You are adorable when you smile.
It's all true
but tell me where you live.
where are we
That is? You live here!
I don't live here.
Seriously?
When did the moon get so close to full?
There are still two days left until the full moon.
What a relief.
Ms. Sin!
A little
- This is from the boss.
- Yes, sir!
- Be careful, okay?
Let's do it!
Remember his face.
Remember. We can…
It hurts! Stupid necklace!
- Pull yourself together!
- Yes, sir!
Spicy and spicy!
- Castor and shallot seeds!
- For him!
- Yes, sir!
Look at me!
- Time to eat.
- Show your face.
These are women!
- Inside!
- Yes, sir!
This is our chance to impress the boss. Let's find him!
who are you
ABRAXAS HAS JOINED THE CHAT
This can become a problem later,
therefore, let's fix everything at the root.
What?
I think it's him.
COINCIDENCE
PROFILE
NAME: KI KWAN CHUL
BLUE NIGHT THEATER
you are here
A most fitting end
for a demon i could invent
there is hellfire.
And he is mentioned in the book.
Spontaneous ignition.
I will do God's work.
let me tell you
that I am not a murderer, but an artist.
you know
what makes people
greater than the devil or God?
People
can become anything.
Either by the devil or by God,
or even something more.
But Suk Mine, son of a bitch.
Did I ever say that?
thank you
that got me out of prison.
I didn't know
that's how I'll repay you.
Devil.
The devil you set free will kill you.
Devil!
Open the door!
But Suk Mine!
This cannot be.
But Suk Mine, so wrong.
Open the door.
Ahoy!
Open the door!
Apart from all the dirty tricks
also murder?
You brought this on yourself, Mom.
I UNDERSTAND
WHAT BIRTH THE DEVIL'S CHILD...
MAYBE MY GUILTY…
PAY FOR YOUR SINS,
AND I WILL PAY FOR MINE
CEO TO TO HI
THE DEVIL
DEMON
The head splits.
hold on
Thank you.
Nothing happened?
Ms. Chu always followed,
so that I don't sound like a drunk.
God, that old woman.
DETECTIVE PAK KYUNG SOO
Yes, detective?
We found the culprit, Ms. To.
We found him, boss.
Castor and shallot seeds found it for you.
We found his hiding place.
His name is Ki Kwang Chul.
There are many cases against him
for murders and assaults.
He is now wanted,
so we can find him soon.
BLUE NIGHT THEATER
Looks more normal than I expected.
This seems like an ordinary man
killed many people.
How did he die?
It was arson.
It is strange that the body was mocked.
Someone stabbed him in the heart
20-centimeter knife
after the body was completely burned.
As if they wanted to leave a message.
It hurts, right?
See you in hell.
What...
To Hee
I heard that the attacker died.
- Yes.
- What happened, detective?
Well…
I have to go check on something.
Can you go home with Choo Seok Hoon?
I heard that the intruder was caught.
What are you looking for?
it's all over
because the intruder is dead, right?
What is it?
Is it a bug?
I was right.
The attacker was killed
for I have seen his face.
How could anyone know
what do you find people by the face?
It is not even written in…
So you understood that we have a bug?
I finally saw the face of the intruder
but the real villain…
hid behind the dead.
- I'm sorry.
- Yes, ma'am?
a minute
Did you just wake up?
Went golfing again?
I have to meet many people
to the shareholders' meeting.
It must be difficult.
- Please continue.
- Yes, ma'am.
You must be shocked.
Yes.
I didn't know
that my proposal to end the war
will meet such a response.
So what does that mean?
It looks like the war is over.
The attacker destroyed his weapon.
Do you really think this is the end?
It should be so.
Everything must come to an end.
The secret of my recovery is a thirst for revenge.
There was no way I could die without paying back
to whoever did this to me.
How did you find the intruder?
You didn't see his face.
Jung Ku Won saw his face,
when he was attacked.
So he found it.
To Hee
Do you trust Mr. Chong a lot?
What are you talking about?
Don't tell me you suspect him.
He would never.
- But To Hee...
- Sok Hune.
Jung Koo Won
always protected me.
Now it's all over.
Time to talk about it.
Let's see if that gets us out
on the real attacker.
Director Chon.
I suggest lying on the bottom.
The knife was a deadly warning.
If the attacker was eavesdropping,
it knows that your powers are not obeyed.
If you act hastily, you will suffer.
And tomorrow will finally be full.
You can become your perfect self again.
So wait just one day and…
Clocks…
What about them?
They stopped.
SEOUL MEDICAL CENTER "HANSE"
I came to visit Lee Yeon Seo
in the pediatric oncology department.
Are you talking about Eun Seo, who has already been discharged?
I heard she is in the hospital again.
This is impossible.
She is a symbol of miracle for our hospital.
- It is falling.
- What is her oxygen level and temperature?
Oxygen is 95% and body temperature is 30.
- Mom is here, Yoon Seo.
- Let's raise the temperature first.
Hang in there sweetie!
Yoon Seo!
Oh no...
Is your name Yoon So?
Do you have a wish?
I hope the parents
will not suffer because of me.
Here is my wish.
My powers didn't just flicker.
They have completely disappeared.
No.
JESUS CORPORATION
BANK "TEKUK"
What?
You know something about me, right?
You have become fully human.
What is going on anyway?
say
For nothing?
Long time no see.
- I will take you to your table, madam.
- Of course.
- They haven't been for a long time.
- You look great.
- Congratulations.
- Hello.
- Long time no see.
- Enjoy yourself.
I always have only two.
Of course, ma'am.
sit down
Do you come here often?
People often judge others by their appearance.
Why are you treated so well?
It is as if they are hypnotized.
I don't know exactly.
They probably see my true strength
despite the appearance.
Give
Thank you.
And this is really the right place
discuss such things?
Really?
What?
You don't like it?
Nothing. It's not your style.
Who…
are you like that
Why are you so surprised?
I can do all the same things as you.
Because I gave you those powers.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
You…
God?
This is one of my names.
Some call me the universe.
Others call me time.
You know, as they say.
"God is everywhere and in everything."
as for me
then it seems that God is nowhere.
Unruly, that's how a demon should be.
Just to think that we flew halfway around the world
for blasphemy.
i believe you
so give me back
my strength
I can't do it.
- What?
- Although I gave you strength,
I did not take them from you.
Did this happen because I didn't sign a new agreement?
Will I get my powers back if I make a deal right away?
Agreements will not change anything.
Since the powers are in the wrong body,
it's only natural that they melt
until they disappear.
Then I…
That's right.
You are dying as we speak.
CHOO SOK HOON
GENERAL DIRECTOR
It seems that To To Hee is very dear to you.
Few people will do so much
even for the closest relatives,
not that cousin.
To Hee is more than family to me.
We have something in common.
So tell me.
Why did you want to see me?
i think you know
who really is Mr. Jeon.
Then how do I get my strength back?
There must be a way.
It's simple.
He is a demon.
Also known as the devil.
You can get your strength back
as soon as that woman dies.
He brings misfortune to people
and leads them to hell.
MY BELOVED DEMON
When the moon is full,
the roulette wheel willstop
and the game ends,
no matter what the result will be.
Let's not stay up all night tonight.
It just seems
it's so wasteful to sleep through the night.
We never went on a honeymoon.
Here we go.
The world without you scares me.
As I said, I will correct you.
The only thing you can do
for him to do is to die.
You mean nothing to me.
I will not back down from any of us.
I choose both myself and To To Hee.
Let's make bets.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel